Good morning, and especially good morning to all of my fellow Black women who find me
quote-unquote annoying, irritating, loud, etc.
This is really something else, and one day you will be revering me, because you will
understand that the reasons that you disliked me had nothing to do with me, and everything
to do with the fact that you were not willing to do the work on yourself that causes you
to hate people like me, who tell you the truth about the world you're in, that you don't
want to believe.
Every time y'all come in my comments and say mean s*** about me, it breaks my heart a little
bit, and then the real ones sew it back together.
So good morning to you real ones.
May the sun bathe upon you and empower you to fight another day for a world that you
believe in can exist.